什么鬼动静
What the hell is that?!
什么鬼动静  是你叫的吗
What the hell is that? Is that you?
-你清晨的火气还真大  -滚远一点
-You're really not a morning person. -Just back off!
起床  起来  快起
Get up! Get up! Get up!
什么声音这么吵
What is that noise?
你的敲门声
You!
是阿鸡啊
It's the chick.
她正经历着过渡时期
She's going through some changes.
什么过渡时期
What kind of changes?
兽医好像认为...
The vet seems to think...
咱们的小母鸡要长大成公鸡了
that she's becoming a rooster.
我们打算再问问别的兽医
We're getting a second opinion.
你干嘛清晨八点去血拼
Why are you shopping at 8 in the morning?
我六点钟就起床了
I've been up since 6...
都是被某人的笨公鸡害的
thanks to somebody's dumb-ass rooster.
你们俩真的应该把它们放生
You guys, you really should get rid of those animals.
它们本不该被圈在公寓里
They shouldn't be living in an apartment.
而且家里的刀和食谱那么多  太不安全了
Especially not with these knives and cookbooks around.
我要去医院的不孕不育科做个检查
All right, I'm going to the fertility doctor
看看我的身体状况是否适合将弗兰克和爱丽丝的
and see if I'm ready to have Frank and Alice's embryo
胚胎移植到我的子宫里去
transferred into my uterus.
医生怎么判断你的身体状况适不适合
How will they know if you are ready?
他们要看看我的子宫内膜是不是已经足够厚了
They'll just gonna look and see if my endometrial layer is thick.
这个检查我可以代劳啊
I can check that for you.
各位  帮我的子宫内膜加油吧
Okay, think ''thick.''
祝你好运
Good luck!
快祝我幸运
Wish me luck.
祝你好运
Good luck.
-我说得准没错  -鬼才信你
- I'm still right. - That is so not true.
怎么了
What?
她不爽是因为我知道  她今天要洗衣服
She's mad because I know today is her laundry day...
所以现在穿的肯定是大妈才穿的那种内裤
and that means she's wearing her old-lady underpants.
要不要我帮你检查一下
I can check that for you.
太不知天高地厚了  你们怎么会觉得
I just can't believe that you think you and Chandler
你和钱德勒对我和瑞秋的了解
know me and Rachel
甚于我们对你俩的了解
better than we know you.
事实如此嘛
Well, we do.
你吃薄荷糖时一定要吃偶数个
You can only eat Tic Tacs in even numbers.
这是什么毛病啊
What's that about?
而你嘛  罗斯  你去搜搜瑞秋的购物袋
And you! Ross, I believe if you check Rachel's bag,
里面肯定有一盒吃了一半的饼干
you'll find a half-eaten box of cookies in there.
你真是神了
You're good.
可饼干馊了
These are not.
有什么了不起  哪有人买东西时不吃零嘴
I'm so not impressed.Everybody snacks when they shop.
是吗  罗斯  购物袋里还剩几样东西
Oh yeah? Ross, how many items left in that bag?
五样
Five.
赌十块  我们能说出五样东西都是什么
Okay, 10 bucks says that we can name every item in that bag.
-猜几次  -六次
- How many guesses you get? - Six.
挑战升级了
Challenge extended.
-赌就赌  -女士们接受挑战
- Deal! - Challenge accepted.
第一样是...苹果
All right, we'll start with...apples.
第一样是苹果
We'll be starting with apples.
拜托你别再用这个腔调了
Stop that now.
有苹果
Yes.
玉米片
Okay. Tortilla chips.
-酸奶  -健怡汽水
- Yogurt. - Diet soda.
有橙汁吗
Orange juice?
没有  我没买橙汁  我们赢了
There's no orange juice! We win!
等等  他们还能再猜一次
They have another guess.
好吧  但是那题我们赢了
Well, we won that one.
最后一样东西是...
Okay. The last thing is...
不是的  不是  还得再过两周
No, no. Not for another two weeks.
我知道了
I got it.
胶...
Scotch...
带
tape.
你怎么知道她会买胶带
How did you know she would buy Scotch tape?
我们昨晚玩扮鬼脸时把她们的胶带用光了
We used up theirs last night making scary faces.
真讨厌
Oh, man!
十块钱  愿赌服输
All right! Ten bucks. Fork it over.
痛快点  拿钱来
Cough it up. Pay the piper.
快给钱
Give me it!
这也说明不了你们俩更了解我们俩啊
It does not mean you know us better.
我要求再比一次  猜杂货太没挑战性了
I want a rematch. And no stupid grocery questions. Real, personal questions.
赌一百块
And the winner gets $ 1 00.
-你当真  -怕了吧
- Serious? - Are you scared?
才怪
No.
谁出考题呢
Who makes up the questions?
让罗斯来
Ross will do it.
是啊  让罗斯来
Sure, Ross will do it.
他难道没工作  没孩子  没有自己的生活吗
Sounds like he hasn't a job or a child or a life of his own.
没关系  那找菲比好了
Fine. We'll ask Phoebe.
不要  人家想玩嘛
No, l want to play.
你的子宫可以做胚胎移植了
Looks like your uterus is ready for implantation.
怪不得我今天一早就觉得自己笨手笨脚
l knew it! I felt really thick this morning.
下面该做什么了  快去取受精卵  植入进去
Okay, so what's now? Go get the eggs. Put them in there.
好的  我去准备那些胚胎  稍等片刻
Okay, it'll take a little while to prepare the embryos.
-那些胚胎  -不只一个吗  其实一共有五个
-Embryos? As in more than one? -Five, actually.
五个呢  那我要在哪儿生孩子啊
Five, okay, where am I giving birth...
在医院还是在楼梯下的大房子里
in a hospital or a big box under the stairs?
我们给你植入五个胚胎是为了
We do five because that gives you a 25% chance
让其中一枚受精卵着床的机率保持在25%
that at least one will attach.
才25%  这么小的概率啊
That's it? 25%?
意味着我怀不上孩子的机率是75%
That means that it's, like, 75% chance of no baby at all?
我在想  如果植入两百个胚胎
You know, I was thinking, what are the odds...
那机率会不会高一点
like if you stuff 200 of them in there?
亲爱的  别傻了...
Sweetie, now...
她是个女人  不是卖泡泡糖的机器
she's a woman, not a gumball machine.
没关系  你们俩别担心
Okay, you know what? Don't worry, you guys.
我会一直坚持做到成功为止
Cause I'll do this as many times as it takes to get it right.
但是我们只有一次机会
The thing is, we kind of only have one shot.
做一次移植要花一万六千块
It costs $16,000 each time you do this.
我们为了这次  已经花光所有的积蓄
So, we're kind of using all the money we have to do it just this one time.
你这样一说  我和我的子宫
Okay, that's a lot of pressure
承担的压力简直太大了
on me and my uterus.
也许我能做些什么事
Well, okay. So maybe there's something I can do
来确保我一定能怀上
you know, to sort of like help make sure I get pregnant.
抱歉  目前没有这种方法
No, I'm sorry.
你们怎么连这个都不知道啊
Wow, you guys really don't know anything.
我知道了  让她喝个烂醉吧
I know. Why don't she get drunk?
我很多高中同学都是这样搞大肚子的
That worked for a bunch of girls in my high school.
伙计们  你们意识到了吗
Guys. Do you realize that any minute now...
菲比现在随时可能会怀孕啊
Phoebe could be pregnant?
我知道...我知道...
I know, I know.
这件事非同小可  足以改变她的生活
It's such a huge, life-altering thing.
每一队都要回答十个问题
Okay. Each team will answer 10 questions.
答对最多的那一队就赢
The first team to answer the most questions wins.
考题项目如下  "恐惧怪癖"
The categories are "Fears and Pet Peeves",
"陈年旧事"
"Ancient History",
"文字往来"
"Literature",
以及"亲朋好友"
and "It's all Relative."
现在
Now...
我们丢硬币来决定哪一队先选题
the coin toss, to see who goes first.
好吧
Okay.
这次拜托你们先猜一下正反面
Somebody call it this time.
反面
Tails!
是正面
It's heads.
男士们  请选择项目
Gentlemen, pick your category.
"恐惧怪癖"
"Fears and Pet Peeves."
"莫妮卡最受不了什么"
"What is Monica's biggest pet peeve?"
-动物穿衣服  -答对了
- Animals dressed as humans. - That's correct.
-女士们  -同一个项目
- Ladies? - Same category.
"用钱德勒自己的话来说
"According to Chandler,
什么能把他吓得魂飞魄散"
what phenomenon scares the bejesus out of him?"
踢踏舞之王  麦克·费特利
Michael Flatley, Lord of the Dance!
答对了
That is correct.
就是那个跳舞的爱尔兰人
The Irish jig guy?
他那双脚跳舞时像要被甩出自己的身体似的
His legs flail about as if independent from his body!
男士们  轮到你们了
Gentlemen, your pick.
"亲朋好友"
"It's all Relative."
"莫妮卡和我的祖母过世时
"Monica and I had a grandmother who died.
两位都参加了她的葬礼
You both went to her funeral.
我们的祖母叫什么名字"
Name that grandmother."
-是婆婆吗  -她有自己的名字吧
- Nana? - She has a real name.
艾席雅
Althea!
-你干什么  -试试看嘛
- What are you doing? - I took a shot!
那干嘛非猜艾席雅
You're shooting with Althea?
-正确答案就是艾席雅  -猜得好
- Althea is correct. - Nice shooting!
我们选"文字往来"
We'll take "Literature."
"乔伊和钱德勒每周都会收到《电视周刊》
''Every week the TV Guide comes to Chandler and Joey's apartment.
请问收件人的姓甚名谁”
What name appears on the address label?''
钱德订的  当然是钱德勒·宾喽
Chandler gets it! Lt's Chandler Bing!
很抱歉  《电视周刊》的收件人的姓名
I'm afraid the TV Guide comes to
是"钱尼德勒·邦"
''Chanandler Bong.''
我知道正确答案
I knew that!
瑞秋  用用脑子行不行
Rachel, use your head!
其实应该是"钱尼德勒·邦小姐"
Actually, it's Ms. Chanandler Bong.
你们好  各位小胚胎
Hello, teeny embryos.
我是菲比·布菲
I'm Phoebe Buffay. Hi!
我很期待在未来的九个月中
I'm hoping to be your uterus
你们能在我的子宫里安家落户
for the next nine months.
我们这么努力都是为了弗兰克和爱丽丝
You should know that we're doing this
你们肯定认识他俩
for Frank and Alice who you know.
因为那儿是第一个家
You've been there.
知道吗  他们真的很希望能有个小宝宝
You know, they want you so much.
我保证会给你们一个安宁而温暖的家
And I promise that I'll keep you safe and warm...
直到你们准备好让他俩带你们回家为止
until you know, you're ready to have them take you home.
咱们下次见面时
And also, next time you see me,
如果听到我大声哭喊  别担心
if I'm screaming, don't worry.
那是很正常的
That's what's supposed to happen.
准备好了吗
Ready?
祝好运
Good luck!
目前比分是九比八  男士领先
All right! The score is nine to eight in favor of the guys.
女士们  你们若答错这题
Ladies, if you miss this,
男士们就赢了  选一个项目吧
the game is theirs. Pick a category.
"亲朋好友"
"It's all Relative"!
-犯不着拉直嗓子吼  -对不起
- You don't have to shout everything. - I'm sorry!
"钱德勒的父亲
"What is the name of Chandler's father's...
在赌城的男子歌舞秀叫做什么名字"
Las Vegas all-male burlesque?"
"拉斯维基斯万岁"
Viva Las Gaygas!
真不幸  你居然答对了
Unfortunately, that is correct.
目前双方平手
All right. We have a tie.
幸好我早有准备
Luckily, I've prepared for such an event.
抢答环节
The lightning round!
双方各有30秒  尽量回答出所有问题
Thirty seconds. All the questions you can answer.
你们输定了
You guys are dead!
我最擅长抢答了
I am so good at lightning rounds!
我大学的专业就是抢答
I majored in lightning rounds, all right?
你们才输定了
We'll destroy you.
敢不敢赌
Want to bet?
怪了  我们这不正在赌着吗
I'm so confused as to what we've been doing so far.
把赌注提高到150块如何
How about we play for more money? Say 150?
150块哦
One hundred and fifty dollars.
200块如何
Say 200?
200块啦
Two hundred dollars!
你又来了
You're doing it again.
不好意思
Excuse me.
-老天  我可不想赔上200块  -不会的
-My God. I don't want to lose $200. -We won't
-300块如何  -莫妮卡
- Three hundred? - Monica!
我只是想让比赛更劲爆  更刺激
I'm just trying to spicing it up!
那赌辣椒行不行  别再乱花我的钱了
So play for some pepper! Stop spending my money.
我有了
I got it!
我们赢的话  他们就得处理掉那只公鸡
If we win, they have to get rid of the rooster.
这主意不赖
That's interesting!
没门  阿鸡和我们是一家人
No way! That rooster's family.
把阿鸭也扔了
The duck too!
阿鸭招你惹你了  它从来不乱叫
What is your problem with the duck? It doesn't make noise!
可是那只鸡被它搞得心浮气躁
He gets the other one all riled up!
-听着  我们绝不  -等等
- Look, we are not... - All right, hold on!
你们赢的话
If you win...
我们就处理掉那只公鸡
we give up the bird.
我们赢的话...
But if we win...
就把你们的公寓让给我们
we get your apartment.
-成交  -什么
- Deal! - What?
莫妮卡  赌上公寓  我心里没底啊
Monica, betting the apartment? I don't know about this.
瑞秋  我从头到尾一道题都没答错
Rachel, I have not missed one question the whole game.
我完全驾驭了这场比赛
I own this game!
-看我的手  -你把答案都抄在手上了吗
-Look at my hand. -You have the answers written there?
不是  我的手稳得很  你还不放心吗
No. Steady as a rock. Now, are you with me?
-咱们上阵吧  -这样才对
- All right, let's do it! - Come on!
男士们  你们先来
All right. Gentlemen, you're up first.
限时抢答30秒
You have 30 seconds.
抢答阶段要开始了...
The lightning round begins...
不准跳
Stop it!
"莫妮卡当曲棍球队守门员时的外号是什么"
"What was Monica's nickname when she was a field hockey goalie?"
-胖大门  -正确
- Big Fat Goalie. - Correct!
"瑞秋对外宣称她最喜欢的电影是什么"
"Rachel claims it's her favorite movie."
-《危险关系》  -正确
- Dangerous Liaisons. - Correct!
"那她真正最喜欢的电影是哪一部"
"Her actual favorite is...?"
-《老板度假去》  -正确
- Weekend at Bernie's. - Correct!
"莫妮卡14岁时
"In what part of her body
身上哪个部位卡了一枝铅笔"
did Monica get a pencil stuck at age 14?"
不是
No!
是她的耳朵
Her ear!
"莫妮卡的毛巾都分门别类  一共分为几类"
''Monica categorizes her towels. How many categories are there?''
-日常毛巾  -高级毛巾
- Everyday use. - Fancy.
-客用毛巾  -高级客用毛巾
- Guest. - Fancy guest.
-还剩两秒钟  -11类
- Two seconds. - Eleven?
就是11  不可思议  答对了
Eleven. Unbelievable! Eleven is correct!
好了
All right.
男士们答对四题  现在轮女士上场
That's four for the guys. Ladies, you're up!
好的  瞧好吧
All right! Come on!
限时抢答30秒
Thirty seconds on the clock.
答对五题你们就赢了
Five correct questions wins the game.
抢答开始  "乔伊最喜欢的食物是什么”
The lightning round begins now. ''Joey's favorite food?''
-三明治  -正确
- Sandwiches! - Correct.
"钱德勒第一次摸女生胸部时几岁"
"Chandler was how old when he first touched a girl's breast?"
-14岁  -错  19
- 14? - No, 19.
谢了  老哥
Thanks, man.
"乔伊小时候有个自己想象的朋友
"Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
他的名字叫什么"
His name was...?"
-莫瑞斯  -正确
-Maurice! -Correct!
"他是干什么的"
''His profession was...?''
-太空牛仔  -正确
- Space cowboy!  - Correct!
"钱德勒·宾干什么工作"
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
跟数字有关
It has something to do with numbers!
-还有数据处理  -他上班带公事包
- And processing! - He carries a briefcase.
剩10秒钟  成败在此一题
Ten seconds. You need this or you lose the game.
跟答询有关
Something to do with transponding.
他是答询员
He's a transponster!
这是你自己造的词
That's not even a word!
我一定能想起来  一定能
I can get this! I can get this!
-不要啊  -太棒啦
-No!  -Yes!
我要莫妮卡的房间
l call Monica's room.
凭什么你说要了  就是你的了
You can't just call Monica's room.
这是规矩  先到先得
Sure I can. Standard shotgun rules.
是我先看到她的房间的  就是我的了
I'm in sight of the room and I called it.
可恶
Damn!
我好像要生病了
I feel like I'm coming down with something.
要不要猜猜我的扁桃腺是什么颜色
Guess what color my tonsils are.
赌上这套公寓
I bet the apartment!
我才不会拿这么棒的公寓来赌呢
I would never bet this apartment. It's too nice.
菲比  胚胎进你的肚子了吗
Oh, Pheebs. Are they in there?
对  胚胎放进去了
Yeah, I'm implanted.
-你觉得怎么样  -担心死了
- How do you feel? - Well, freaked.
成功怀上的机率竟然很低
It turns out the odds are really sucky.
而弗兰克和爱丽丝只有这一次机会
And this is Frank and Alice's...like...only shot.
他们真的是把所有的蛋都放在我的篮子里了
They are like literally putting all their eggs in my basket.
我相信你一定会成功
But I bet it works.
是吗  你要赌多少
Really? How much?
我现在要去验孕
All right, I'm gonna go to take a pregnancy test right now.
这么快就能知道怀没怀上了
Wow! You can tell this soon?
医生说要等两天
The doctor says it takes a few days.
但是我的身体一向比西方医学预估的快一点
But my body's always been a little faster than Western medicine.
天呐  你们俩真的以为
Oh, my God. I can't believe you guys think
这儿是你们的家了吗
you're moving in here.
面对现实吧  宝贝
Well, believe it, baby!
-我可不走  -什么
- Well, I'm not moving. - What?
那不过是场愚蠢的赌局  不过是玩玩罢了
No. It was a stupid bet. We were just playing a game.
赌了就是赌了  哪能不算
You can't ignore the bet. It's a bet!
你得认赌服输啊
Bet on a bet and if you lose, you lose the bet.
瑞秋  我们非搬不可了
Rachel, we have to move.
若我们赢了也会逼他们
If they lose, we would have made them
把鸡鸭处理掉  对吧
get rid of the birds, right?
我才没那么狠心
No.
我也不想这样  但说句安慰你的话
l hate this as much as you, but if it makes you feel better...
这全都是你的错
this is all your fault.
什么
What?
我们每周都偷他们的《电视周刊》
Chanandler Bong!
你怎么会不知道收件人是钱尼德勒·邦
We steal that TV Guide every week!
我就知道是你们偷的
I knew it!
我不管  反正我不走
I don't care. I'm not going anywhere.
那也不错  跟女生做室友
Cool! Girl roommate.
怎么样
Well?
没有  还没怀上呢
Nope, not knocked up yet.
才过了几个小时  你太心急了
It's only been a couple hours, you just skip the time.
我还是想自己努努力  加快一下速度
Meanwhile, I'll do whatever I can to help this.
借我你们的椅子躺一躺
I'm just going to, you know, lie in your chair, okay?
挺好  让地心引力发挥作用
Good. I'm going to let gravity do its job.
瑞秋  顺便告诉你
Oh, Rach, FYl: Your new
你的新公寓自从圣诞节就没热水了
apartment hasn't had hot water since Christmas.
不  把箱子放下来  我们哪儿都不去
No! Put that box down! We are not going anywhere!
这是我的公寓  我喜欢它
This is my apartment and I like it!
这是女生的公寓
This is a girl's apartment!
那里才是又脏又臭的男生公寓
That is a boy's apartment! It's dirty and it smells!
这里漂亮极了  太漂亮了
This is pretty! It's so pretty!
看  墙壁是紫的
And look, it's purple!
告诉你  稳若磐石小姐  我不搬
I tell you, you with your steady hand, I am not moving.
看  我的手现在也稳若磐石
And now I have got the steady hand.
-我去搞定  -这就对了
- I'll take care of it. - That's right.
听我手的指挥
You do what the hand says!
-战况如何  -我把床垫也输掉了
- How'd it go? - I lost our mattresses.
小小胎儿  你可听得到
Are you in there, little fetus?
九个月后  你是否就将来到
In nine months will you come greet us?
阿迪达斯  我一定亲手送到
I will buy you some Adidas.
菲比  你好
Hi, Phoebe!
我们刚刚去过药店
We were just at the drugstore
帮你买了个小礼物
so we got you a little present.
棒棒糖和验孕棒
It's a lollipop and a home pregnancy test.
千万别搞混了  要不然棒棒糖可就没法吃了
Don't mix those up. You could really ruin that lollipop.
想不想测验一下  这个测试仅此一项哦
You feel like taking a test? There's only one question.
我验就是了
All right. I will.
别忘了  现在为时尚早
But, just remember that it's still really early.
若结果是阴性
If it says I'm not pregnant,
不表示我一定就怀不上了
that doesn't mean I won't get pregnant.
如果你们不想让我被压力逼疯的话
Just please, just so I don't go completely nuts...
拜托你们别把期望全部寄托在我身上
just try not to put all your hopes on this.
好
Great.
你们真是太刻薄了  刻薄到家了
You know what? Yor are mean boys who are just being mean!
别把气出在我们身上
Don't get mad!
没人逼你们一直抬高赌注
No one forced you to raise the stakes.
胡说  她逼我了  是她
That is not true! She did, she forced me!
如果你没答错那道题  我们就不用搬了
We'll still be living here if you hadn't got the question wrong.
那个问题太愚蠢  太不公平了
That is a stupid, unfair question!
别怪我出的问题
Don't blame the questions!
别在我们家大吵大闹  扫了我们的搬家兴
Would you all stop yelling in our apartment! You are ruining moving day for us.
-别说这里是你们家  -本来就是我们家
-Would you stop calling it your apartment! -It is our apartment!
伙计们  你们要有宝宝了
Guys! You're going to have a baby.
他们要有自己的宝宝了
They're going to have a baby!
我姐姐要帮我生小孩了
My sister's going to have my baby!
谢谢大家  不过别抱了  对宝宝不好
Okay, but this can't be good for the baby.
我找不到垃圾袋
I can't find garbage bags.
这里面好像有
I think I saw some in here.
什么东西
What is it?
不知道  不过要是一直不开抽屉
I don't know. But maybe if we keep that drawer shut,
它也许会死
it'll die.
真不敢相信我们得住在这里
I can't believe we're living here!
怎么了
What is it?
你知道衣橱有多大吗
Did you see the size of the closets?
真不敢相信咱们能住在这里
I can't believe we live here!